https://www.wifvne.org/privacy-policy

PRIVACY POLICY
Women In Film & Video/New England (WIFV/NE) strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. Please note this policy applies only to information collected by WIFV/NE online and does not impact information collected or used by WIFV/NE or its affiliates through other means.
WHO IS COLLECTING YOUR INFORMATION:Your information is being collected solely by  WIFVNE. See the discussion below under “With whom your information may be shared” concerning the circumstances under which we may disclose certain of your information to third parties.
HOW WE GATHER INFORMATION FROM USERS:How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. You can visit many pages on our site without providing any information. Other pages may prompt you to provide information, such as when you register for access to portions of our site, sign up for membership, request certain features (e.g., newsletters, news updates and other products), sign up for a subscription or make a purchase. You may also provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests, voting and polling activities, surveys and questionnaires, message boards and chat rooms and other interactive areas of our site.
Like most Web sites, WIFV/NE also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use “cookie” technology. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but doing so may limit your ability to access certain portions of the site or may require you to re-enter your user name and password. Additionally we may not be able to customize the site’s features according to your preferences.
WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT:We will use your information only as permitted by law. Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. As one example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive. Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners, but cannot be used to contact you individually.
We also collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and advertising. For example, we may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on WIFV/NE to communicate with you regarding our programs, events, Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, products and services offered by WIFV/NE and other WIFV/NE affiliates and partners, administration of sweepstakes and contests, surveys, processing e-commerce transactions and other topics we think you might find of interest.
Personally Identifiable Information collected by WIFV/NE may also be used for other purposes including but not limited to site administration and troubleshooting. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service and our newsletter provider, for example) may access such information.
As we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary to give such information to law enforcement authorities. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.
WITH WHOM YOUR INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED:WIFV/NE does not sell, trade, or rent your personally identifiable information to others. We may disclose information to an affiliated party. In such an instance, your information would not be used in any manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy without your prior permission.
RETENTION OF INFORMATION:
Any information we collect may be retained for an indeterminate period of time.
YOUR CHOICE TO OPT OUT:If you prefer not to receive e-mail communications sent directly from WIFV/NE, you will be given an opportunity to decline before you provide us information we might use for this purpose. If you decline at the time you provide us such information, we will not share the Personally Identifiable Information you provide with non-Affiliated advertisers for such purposes, though we may on occasion send you information on their behalf.
AFFILIATED SITES, LINKED SITES AND ADVERTISEMENTS:WIFV/NE expects its partners, members, contributors and third-party affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. However, third parties, including our partners, members, contributors, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a WIFV/NE page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through WIFV/NE you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, advertisements, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. WIFV/NE is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.
Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. Should you choose to voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on our site, such as in message boards, chat areas or in advertising or notices you post, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of WIFV/NE and this policy.
PUBLIC FORUMS:This Website may make discussion boards, groups and/or other public forums available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed to these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personally identifiable information.
CHILDREN:This Website is not directed at persons under 18 years of age and our content and other services are not written, intended, or designed for persons under 18 years of age. We do not intend to collect any personally identifiable information from such individuals. Where appropriate,  WIFV/NE will specifically instruct children not to submit such information on the Website. If a child has provided us with personally identifiable information, a parent or guardian of that child should contact us at the mailing address or e-mail address listed at the bottom of this Privacy Policy if he or she would like this information deleted from our records. We will use reasonable efforts to delete the child’s information from our existing files.
CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY:WIFV/NE has implemented generally accepted security standards to protect information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Only employees and registered users of WIFV/NE have access to the information we collect, and these employees and registered users are made aware of and required to comply with our Privacy Policy.  Any personal information you give out online – such as in discussion boards or groups — may be collected and used by people you do not know.  While  WIFV/NE strives to protect your information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any such information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk.
The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our users and members is of utmost concern to us. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information,  WIFV/NE cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you agree to transmit such information to us at your own risk. Once we receive your personally identifiable information, we will take reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems.
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY:WIFV/NE reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.  This page sets forth our Privacy Policy as of March, 2012. All versions of this Privacy Policy are dated with the effective date (the date on which the policy was posted to the Website).  We will only use the information we learn about you in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect when the information was collected from you. However, we reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revisions to our site.
GOVERNING LAW:These Terms of Use will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Massachusetts, without regard to principles of conflicts or choice of law. In addition, the application of the United Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods, including any amendments thereto, is expressly excluded hereby. Except for disputes arising from an alleged violation of intellectual property rights or breach of confidentiality, for which the injured party may suffer irreparable harm and may seek a restraining order, preliminary injunctive relief, an injunction, specific performance or other equitable relief and/or legal remedies, and actions to enforce the decisions of the arbitrators, for which action may be taken in any court of competent jurisdiction, all disputes arising out of or related to this Agreement, including the scope, the construction or application of this Agreement, shall be resolved by arbitration in accordance with the commercial arbitration rules of the American Arbitration Association then in force. The arbitration hearings and all meetings pursuant to this section shall be held in Boston, Massachusetts, USA, and shall be conducted in English. If the parties cannot agree upon a single arbitrator within fifteen (15) days after demand by either of them, each party shall select one arbitrator knowledgeable about Internet commerce in Massachusetts and the USA generally, and notify the other of its selection, and such two arbitrators shall select a third from a list of arbitrators (with knowledge of the Internet industry) qualified by the American Arbitration Association in Massachusetts. If this procedure for selecting arbitrators fails, then a neutral arbitrator based in Massachusetts with knowledge of Internet commerce in Massachusetts and the USA generally shall be selected by the American Arbitration Association to resolve the dispute. The arbitrator(s) shall conduct a hearing within thirty (30) days after their selection. A majority of the arbitrators (if there is more than one pursuant to this clause) shall determine the decision/award, which shall be rendered within five (5) days after the completion of the hearing. The decision of the arbitrator(s) shall be final and binding upon the parties both as to law and to fact, and shall not be appealable to any court in any jurisdiction. The parties shall share the expenses of the arbitrators equally. Nothing in any indemnification provision hereunder shall be construed as having any bearing on the award of attorneys’ fees or arbitrators’ fees under this section. If you are located outside the United States, please note the information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. You hereby consent to this transfer.
In the event case of any conflict between the terms of this policy and the terms of any electronic or machine readable privacy policy (for example, a P3P electronic privacy policy), the terms of this written policy shall control.
QUESTIONS:If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:
By Mail:
Women In Film & Video, New England
P.O. Box 118
East Boston, MA 02128
By E-Mail:
info@wifvne.org
Log in
Forgot password
Women In Film & Video, New EnglandP.O. Box 118East Boston, MA 02128info@womeninfilmvideo.org
© 2020 Women in Film & Video New England. All Rights Reserved.
Manage your Membership Easier
Powered by Wild Apricot Membership Software
